

DILNOZA NESHCHERET

JUNIOR UX | UI DESIGNER
TRAINEE FRONT-END DEVELOPER

HARD SKILLS

- Figma
- Low and high fidelity prototypes
- Adaptive design
- Typography
- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript

SOFT SKILLS

- Attentive
- Calm
- Communicate
- Reliable
- · Eanger to learn
- Honest

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- English Pre-intermediate
- Ukrainian Native
- Russian Native

CONTACT DETAILS

+38 (063) 054-49-90 (viber, telegram) dilnozaneshcheret@gmail.com

Behance

<u>Device Battle</u> design project

GitHub

ABOUT ME

I'm studying front-end development. I worked in the project as a web designer and was involved in website layout (html/css, vue.js). I'm ready to study development and can combine it with design.

I specialize in UI|UX design for web and mobile applications. I bring ideas to life to solve client problems and create aesthetic solutions. I am engaged in full-cycle design: I analyze the task, prototype the interface, create a visual style and embody all this into a convenient and simple final product. Let's create something great together.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Website "Device Battle"

A website about comparing phones and other devices using Al. The design of the site was completely done by me, somewhere I collaborated with the developers directly and together we decided how best to make the design.

GitHub

There are projects on github that I did during my studies. I also started doing Front-end Web Development with HTML/CSS on Device Battle.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UI | UX Design (2022-2024)

I have experience in ukrainian company SmartExpert (6 month) after study. Then I worked on the project Device Battle for a year. We had work calls every day and together we solved one or another problem.

Device Battle project (2022-2023)

All UX|UI Design and some <u>Front-end Web Development</u> with HTML/CSS.

EDUCATION

GoIT Academy

Web-Design | 2022 Front-End Developer | 2023

National Aviation University

Department of Computer Information Technologies | 2013-2018